Guide to the Harlequin Romance Collection of Treva M. Taylor 1967-1996 (Bulk 1974-1996) MSS.216
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Harlequin Romance Novels
  - Harlequin Romance 2024. MacLeod, Jean S.: Journey into Spring. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2025. Neels, Betty: Roses for Christmas. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 343)
  - Harlequin Romance 2026. Gillen, Lucy: The House of Kingdom. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2027. Donnelly, Jane: The Silver Cage. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 344)
  - Harlequin Romance 2028. Mayo, Margaret: Perilous Waters. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2029. Gray, Janice: A Kiss for Apollo. (Halrequin Books), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 345)
  - Harlequin Romance 2030. Peters, Sue: One Special Rose. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2031. Wibberley, Mary: The Moon-dancers. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 346)
  - Harlequin Romance 2032. Hunter, Elizabeth: The Bride Price. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2033. Arbor, Jane: Tree of Paradise. (Harlequin Books), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 347)
  - Harlequin Romance 2034. Lees, Marguerite: Green Folly. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2035. Chace, Isobel: A Canopy of Rose Leaves. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 15, Folder 348)
  - Harlequin Romance 2036. Stratton, Rebecca: The Road to Gafsa. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2037. Malcolm, Margaret: Flight to Fantasy. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 15, Folder 349)
  - Harlequin Romance 2038. Corrie, Jane: Sinclair Territory. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2039. Britt, Katrina: If Today Be Sweet. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 15, Folder 350)
  - Harlequin Romance 2040. Hilliard, Nerina: Sister to Meryl. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2041. Neels, Betty: The Edge of Winter. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 15, Folder 351)
  - Harlequin Romance 2042. Danbury, Iris: The Scented Island. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2043. Burchell, Mary: Elusive Harmony. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 15, Folder 352)
  - Harlequin Romance 2044. Ashton, Elizabeth: Mountain Heritage. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2045. Caine, Rebecca: Child of Tahiti. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 15, Folder 353)
  - Harlequin Romance 2046. Thorpe, Kay: Safari South. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2047. Dingwell, Joyce: Inland Paradise. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 15, Folder 354)
  - Harlequin Romance 2048. Hunter, Elizabeth: The Realms of Gold. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2048. Reid, Henrietta: The Tartan Ribbon. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 15, Folder 355)
  - Harlequin Romance 2050. Stratton, Rebecca: Gemini Child. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2051. Mayo, Margaret: Land of Ice and Fire. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 356)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233406
  - Harlequin Romance 2052. Rome, Margaret: Bride of Zarco. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2053. Corrie, Jane: Green Paddocks. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 357)
  - Harlequin Romance 2054. Elver, Rose: Fire Mountain. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2055. Charlton, Madeline: A Sense of Words. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 358)
  - Harlequin Romance 2056. Kidd, Flora: The Black Knight. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2057. Cork, Dorothy: Dreamtime at Big Sky. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 359)
  - Harlequin Romance 2058. Pargeter, Margaret: Blue Skies, Dark Water. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2059. Wibberley, Mary: The Silver Link. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 360)
  - Harlequin Romance 2060. Way, Margaret: The Man on the Half-Moon. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2061. Burchell, Mary: Honey. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 361)
  - Harlequin Romance 2062. Graham, Elizabeth: The Girl from Finlay's River. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2063. Neels, Betty: A Gem of a Girl. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 362)
  - Harlequin Romance 2064. Donnelly, Jane: The Intruder. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2065. Chace, Isobel: The Whistling Thorn. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 363)
  - Harlequin Romance 2066. Arbor, Jane: Two Pins in a Fountain. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2067. Pollock, Rosemary: Summer Comes Slowly. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 364)
  - Harlequin Romance 2068. Summers, Essie: Goblin Hill. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2069. Beaty, Betty: Fly Away, Love. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 365)
  - Harlequin Romance 2070. Britt, Katrina: The Villa Faustino. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2071. Smith, Doris E.: Wild Heart. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 366)
  - Harlequin Romance 2072. Corrie, Jane: The Bahamian Prince. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2073. Bevan, Gloria: Bachelor Territory. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 367)
  - Harlequin Romance 2074. Way, Margaret: Swan's Reach. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2075. Lewty, Marjorie: To Catch a Butterfly. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 368)
  - Harlequin Romance 2076. Ashton, Elizabeth: Aegean Quest. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2077. Whittal, Yvonne: Devil's Getaway. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 369)
  - Harlequin Romance 2078. Stratton, Rebecca: Girl in a White Hat. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2079. Thorpe, Kay: The River Lord. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 370)
  - Harlequin Romance 2080. Neels, Betty: A Small Slice of Summer. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2081. Westwood, Gwen: Bride of Bonamour. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 371)
  - Harlequin Romance 2082. Hampson, Anne: Call of the Outback. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2083. Lamb, Charlotte: Festival Summer. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 372)
  - Harlequin Romance 2084. Bianchin, Helen: Avenging Angel. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2085. Wibberley, Mary: Dark Venturer. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 373)
  - Harlequin Romance 2086. Mayo, Margaret: Rainbow Magic. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2087. Corrie, Jane: Dangerous Alliance. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 374)
  - Harlequin Romance 2088. Graham, Elizabeth: The Shores of Eden. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2089. Gray, Janice: Green for a Season. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 375)
  - Harlequin Romance 2090. Donnelly, Jane: Dear Caliban. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2091. Stratton, Rebecca: Inherit the Sun. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 376)
  - Harlequin Romance 2092. Gillen, Lucy: Master of Ben Ross. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2093. Ashton, Elizabeth: Voyage of Enchantment. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 377)
  - Harlequin Romance 2094. Allyne, Kerry: Bound for Marandoo. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2095. Neels, Betty: A Matter of Chance. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 378)
  - Harlequin Romance 2096. Rome, Margaret: The Thistle and the Rose. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2097. Douglas, Sheila: The Reluctant Neighbour (original title: The Doctor Next Door). (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 17, Folder 379)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233414
  - Harlequin Romance 2098. Corrie, Jane: Rimmer's Way. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2099. Hampson, Anne: Boss of Bali Creek. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 17, Folder 380)
  - Harlequin Romance 2100. May, Wynne: A Plantation of Vines. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2101. Whittal, Yvonne: Where Seagulls Cry. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 17, Folder 381)
  - Harlequin Romance 2102. Gilbert, Jacqueline: Every Wise Man. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2103. Lamb, Charlotte: Florentine Spring. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 17, Folder 382)
  - Harlequin Romance 2104. Peters, Sue: Portrait of Paradise. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2105. Wibberley, Mary: Wildcat Tamed. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 17, Folder 383)
  - Harlequin Romance 2106. Stratton, Rebecca: More Than a Dream. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2107. Lane, Roumelia: Bamboo Wedding. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 17, Folder 384)
  - Harlequin Romance 2108. Arbor, Jane: A Growing Moon. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2109. Thorpe, Kay: Storm Passage. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 17, Folder 385)
  - Harlequin Romance 2110. Neels, Betty: The Hasty Marriage. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2111. Way, Margaret: One-Way Ticket. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 17, Folder 386)
  - Harlequin Romance 2112. Pargeter, Margaret: Never Go Back. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2113. Reid, Henrietta: Push the Past Behind (original title: Dear Tyrant). (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 17, Folder 387)
  - Harlequin Romance 2114. Chace, Isobel: The Mouth of Truth. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2115. Cork, Dorothy: Breakers on the Beach. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 17, Folder 388)
  - Harlequin Romance 2116. Ashton, Elizabeth: Green Harvest. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2117. Ford, Norrey: The Fountain of Love. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 17, Folder 389)
  - Harlequin Romance 2118. Mayo, Margaret: Sea Gypsy. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2119. Hampson, Anne: Moon without Stars. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 17, Folder 390)
  - Harlequin Romance 2120. Hunter, Elizabeth: Pride of Madeira. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2121. Britt, Katrina: The Faithful Heart. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 17, Folder 391)
  - Harlequin Romance 2122. Danbury, Iris: The Painted Palace. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2123. Dingwell, Joyce: A Drift of Jasmine. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 17, Folder 392)
  - Harlequin Romance 2124. Donnelly, Jane: Four Weeks in Winter. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2125. Chapman, Margaret: The Gift of Love. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 17, Folder 393)
  - Harlequin Romance 2126. Graham, Elizabeth: Fraser's Bride. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2127. Neels, Betty: Grasp a Nettle. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 17, Folder 394)
  - Harlequin Romance 2128. Whittal, Yvonne: Price of Happiness. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2129. Weston, Sophie: Wife to Charles. (Harlequin Books), 1977 (Box 17, Folder 395)
  - Harlequin Romance 2130. Hampson, Anne: Isle of Desire. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2131. Stratton, Rebecca: The Sign of the Ram. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 17, Folder 396)
  - Harlequin Romance 2132. Way, Margaret: Black Ingo. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2133. Summers, Essie: Adair of Starlight Peaks. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 17, Folder 397)
  - Harlequin Romance 2134. Gillen, Lucy: Heron's Point. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2135. Hilton, Margery: The House of Strange Music. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 17, Folder 398)
  - Harlequin Romance 2136. Wibberley, Mary: Daughter of the Sun. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2137. Neels, Betty: Pineapple Girl. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 17, Folder 399)
  - Harlequin Romance 2138. Hampson, Anne: Sweet is the Web. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2139. Cork, Dorothy: Outback Rainbow. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 17, Folder 400)
  - Harlequin Romance 2140. Pargeter, Margaret: Flamingo Moon. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2141. Stratton, Rebecca: The Velvet Glove. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 17, Folder 401)
  - Harlequin Romance 2142. MacLeod, Jean S.: Island Stranger. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2143. Britt, Katrina: The Silver Tree. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 402)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233422
  - Harlequin Romance 2144. Lewty, Marjorie: The Time and the Loving. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2145. Way, Margaret: Portrait of Jaime. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 403)
  - Harlequin Romance 2146. Kidd, Flora: To Play with Fire. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2147. Wibberley, Mary: Wild Goose. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 404)
  - Harlequin Romance 2148. Summers, Essie: Spring in September. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2149. Bevan, Gloria: Plantation Moon. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 405)
  - Harlequin Romance 2150. Donnelly, Jane: Touched by Fire. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2151. Thorpe, Kay: Timber Boss. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 406)
  - Harlequin Romance 2152. Rome, Margaret: Lion of Venice. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2153. Neels, Betty: The Little Dragon. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 407)
  - Harlequin Romance 2154. Stratton, Rebecca: Dream of Winter. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2155. Wentworth, Sally: Island Masquerade. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 408)
  - Harlequin Romance 2156. Peters, Sue: Lure of the Falcon. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2157. Chapman, Margaret: Night of the Moon. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 409)
  - Harlequin Romance 2158. Clemence, Ruth: Man with a Mission. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2159. Corrie, Jane: Rafferty's Legacy. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 410)
  - Harlequin Romance 2160. Hampson, Anne: The Shadow Between. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2161. Lamb, Charlotte: Hawk in a Blue Sky. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 411)
  - Harlequin Romance 2162. Whittal, Yvonne: Handful of Stardust. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2163. Hampson, Anne: Fly Beyond the Sunset. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 412)
  - Harlequin Romance 2164. Dingwell, Joyce: Year of the Dragon. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2165. Rothwell, Una: A Long Way to Go. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 413)
  - Harlequin Romance 2166. Beaty, Betty: Master at Arms. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2167. Corrie, Jane: Patterson's Island. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 414)
  - Harlequin Romance 2168. Pargeter, Margaret: Wild Inheritance. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2169. Neels, Betty: Britannia All at Sea. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 415)
  - Harlequin Romance 2170. Graham, Elizabeth: Heart of the Eagle. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2171. Britt, Katrina: The Enchanted Woods. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 416)
  - Harlequin Romance 2172. Ashton, Elizabeth: Breeze from the Bosphorous. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2173. Stratton, Rebecca: Spindrift. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 417)
  - Harlequin Romance 2174. Way, Margaret: Mutiny in Paradise. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2175. Bianchin, Helen: The Hills of Home. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 418)
  - Harlequin Romance 2176. Chace, Isobel: Second Best Wife. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2177. Wibberley, Mary: Lord of the Island. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 419)
  - Harlequin Romance 2178. Gillen, Lucy: Back of Beyond. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2179. Ashton, Elizabeth: The Questing Heart. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 420)
  - Harlequin Romance 2180. Stratton, Rebecca: Image of Love. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2181. Lamb, Charlotte: Master of Comus. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 421)
  - Harlequin Romance 2182. Hampson, Anne: Under Moonglow. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2183. Pargeter, Margaret: Better to Forget. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 422)
  - Harlequin Romance 2184. Allyne, Kerry: Tuesday's Jillaroo. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2185. Wentworth, Sally: King of the Castle. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 423)
  - Harlequin Romance 2186. Hampson, Anne: Call of the Veld. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2187. Donnelly, Jane: The Black Hunter. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 19, Folder 424)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233430
  - Harlequin Romance 2188. Way, Margaret: The Wild Swan. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2189. Dingwell, Joyce: Remember September. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 19, Folder 425)
  - Harlequin Romance 2190. Graham, Elizabeth: Mason's Ridge. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2191. MacLeod, Jean S.: Search for Yesterday. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 19, Folder 426)
  - Harlequin Romance 2192. Ashton, Elizabeth: The Golden Girl. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2193. Pargeter, Margaret: Midnight Magic. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 19, Folder 427)
  - Harlequin Romance 2194. Corrie, Jane: The Texan Rancher. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2195. Donnelly, Jane: Love for a Stranger. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 19, Folder 428)
  - Harlequin Romance 2196. Lewty, Marjorie: The Short Engagement. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2197. Clair, Daphne: A Streak of Gold. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 19, Folder 429)
  - Harlequin Romance 2198. Whittal, Yvonne: Scars of Yesterday. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2199. Cork, Dorothy: A Thousand Miles Away. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 19, Folder 430)
  - Harlequin Romance 2200. Ashton, Elizabeth: Rendezvous in Venice. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2201. Stratton, Rebecca: Bargain for Paradise. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 19, Folder 431)
  - Harlequin Romance 2202. Neels, Betty: Philomena's Miracle. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2203. Way, Margaret: The Awakening Flame. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 19, Folder 432)
  - Harlequin Romance 2204. Peters, Sue: Entrance to the Harbour. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2205. Allyne, Kerry: The Wool King. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 19, Folder 433)
  - Harlequin Romance 2206. Lamb, Charlotte: Desert Barbarian. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2207. Wentworth, Sally: Conflict in Paradise. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 19, Folder 434)
  - Harlequin Romance 2208. Stanford, Sondra: A Stranger's Kiss. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2209. Corrie, Jane: Peacock's Walk. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 19, Folder 435)
  - Harlequin Romance 2210. MacLean, Jan: To Begin Again. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2211. Pargeter, Margaret: The Jewelled Cartan. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 19, Folder 436)
  - Harlequin Romance 2212. Britt, Katrina: Open Not the Door. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2213. Hilton, Margery: The Dark Side of Marriage. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 19, Folder 437)
  - Harlequin Romance 2214. Gilbert, Jacqueline: Country Cousin. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2215. Hampson, Anne: Leaf in the Storm. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 19, Folder 438)
  - Harlequin Romance 2216. Dingwell, Joyce: All the Days of Summer. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2217. Donnelly, Jane: Spell of the Seven Stones. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 19, Folder 439)
  - Harlequin Romance 2218. Weston, Sophie: Unexpected Hazard. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2219. Pollock, Rosemary: Tiger in Darkness. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 19, Folder 440)
  - Harlequin Romance 2220. Peake, Lilian: Rebel in Love. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2221. Wibberley, Mary: The Taming of Tamsin. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 19, Folder 441)
  - Harlequin Romance 2222. Stratton, Rebecca: The Corsican Bandit. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2223. Graham, Elizabeth: New Man at Cedar Hills. (Harlequin Books), 1978 (Box 19, Folder 442)
  - Harlequin Romance 2224. Bevan, Gloria: Fringe of Heaven. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2225. Dingwell, Joyce: The Boss's Daughter. (Harlequin Books), 1979 (Box 19, Folder 443)
  - Harlequin Romance 2226. Neels, Betty: Never While the Grass Grows. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2227. Pargeter, Margaret: The Wild Rowan. (Harlequin Books), 1979 (Box 19, Folder 444)
  - Harlequin Romance 2228. Kidd, Flora: The Bargain Bride. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2229. Lane, Roumelia: Hidden Rapture. (Harlequin Books), 1979 (Box 19, Folder 445)
  - Harlequin Romance 2230. Hampson, Anne: Harbour of Love. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2231. Arbor, Jane: Return to Silbersee. (Harlequin Books), 1979 (Box 19, Folder 446)
  - Harlequin Romance 2232. Thorpe, Kay: The Wilderness Trail. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2233. Hampson, Anne: To Tame a Vixen. (Harlequin Books), 1979 (Box 19, Folder 447)
  - Harlequin Romance 2234. Thorpe, Kay: Full Circle. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2235. Rome, Margaret: Son of Adam. (Harlequin Books), 1979 (Box 19, Folder 448)
  - Harlequin Romance 2236. Naughton, Lee: Sand through My Fingers. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2237. Graham, Elizabeth: Return to Silvercreek. (Harlequin Books), 1979 (Box 20, Folder 449)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142042233448
  - Harlequin Romance 2238. Britt, Katrina: The Hills Beyond. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2239. Summers, Essie: The Lake of the Kingfisher. (Harlequin Books), 1979 (Box 20, Folder 450)
  - Harlequin Romance 2240. Barrie, Susan: Victoria and the Nightingale. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2241. Pargeter, Margaret: A Man Called Cameron. (Harlequin Books), 1979 (Box 20, Folder 451)
  - Harlequin Romance 2242. Cork, Dorothy: Forget and Forgive. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2243. Whittal, Yvonne: Magic of the Baobab. (Harlequin Books), 1979 (Box 20, Folder 452)
  - Harlequin Romance 2244. Elver, Rose: Tiger Sky. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2245. Wibberley, Mary: Witchwood. (Harlequin Books), 1979 (Box 20, Folder 453)
  - Harlequin Romance 2246. Hampson, Anne: For Love of a Pagan. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2247. Ashton, Elizabeth: The Willing Hostage. (Harlequin Books), 1979 (Box 20, Folder 454)
  - Harlequin Romance 2248. Allyne, Kerry: West of the Waminda. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2249. Whittal, Yvonne: Love is Eternal. (Harlequin Books), 1979 (Box 20, Folder 455)
  - Harlequin Romance 2250. Neels, Betty: Ring in a Teacup. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2251. Arbor, Jane: Late Rapture. (Harlequin Books), 1979 (Box 20, Folder 456)
  - Harlequin Romance 2252. Malcolm, Margaret: Summer's Lease. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2253. Cork, Dorothy: Heart of the Whirlwind. (Harlequin Books), 1979 (Box 20, Folder 457)
  - Harlequin Romance 2254. Wentworth, Sally: Rightful Possession. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2255. Donnelly, Jane: Forest of the Night. (Harlequin Books), 1979 (Box 20, Folder 458)
  - Harlequin Romance 2256. Ashton, Elizabeth: The Garden of the Gods. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2257. Corrie, Jane: The Island Bride. (Harlequin Books), 1979 (Box 20, Folder 459)
  - Harlequin Romance 2258. Way, Margaret: Wake the Sleeping Tiger. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2259. Cork, Dorothy: Island of Escape. (Harlequin Books), 1979 (Box 20, Folder 460)
  - Harlequin Romance 2260. Pargeter, Margaret: Marriage Impossible. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2261. Stratton, Rebecca: Lost Heritage. (Harlequin Books), 1979 (Box 20, Folder 461)
  - Harlequin Romance 2262. Wentworth, Sally: Liberated Lady. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2263. Graham, Elizabeth: Man from Down Under. (Harlequin Books), 1979 (Box 20, Folder 462)
  - Harlequin Romance 2264. Rome, Margaret: Isle of Calypso. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2265. Way, Margaret: The Winds of Heaven. (Harlequin Books), 1979 (Box 20, Folder 463)
  - Harlequin Romance 2266. Hampson, Anne: South of the Moon. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2267. Wibberley, Mary: Love's Sweet Revenge. (Harlequin Books), 1979 (Box 20, Folder 464)
  - Harlequin Romance 2268. Stratton, Rebecca: The Eagle of the Vincella. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2269. Britt, Katrina: The Midnight Sun. (Harlequin Books), 1979 (Box 20, Folder 465)
  - Harlequin Romance 2270. Donnelly, Jane: Behind a Closed Door. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2271. Jeffrey, Elizabeth: Shadow of Celia. (Harlequin Books), 1979 (Box 20, Folder 466)
  - Harlequin Romance 2272. Hampson, Anne: Where the South Wind Blows. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2273. Woolf, Victoria: Sweet Compulsion. (Harlequin Books), 1979 (Box 20, Folder 467)
  - Harlequin Romance 2274. Stratton, Rebecca: Lark in an Alien Sky. (Harlequin Books); Harlequin Romance 2275. Neels, Betty: Sun and Candlelight. (Harlequin Books), 1979 (Box 20, Folder 468)